Dream Wedding is a tv movie, comedy, romance film
directed by Scott Corban Sikma.
Sisters Kate and Megan attend their local wedding fair they jokingly enter a
dream wedding package even though they are not getting married.
Surprise the sisters win and now must put on a show or be
mortified by their champagne decisions.
Andy Swenson, played by Jesse Hutch.
Kate Wilde, played by Rebecca Dalton.
Joanne McKenzie, played by Amy Matysio.
Kari, played by Laura Yenga.
Wedding Guest, played by Bud Klasky.
Mike, played by Pardeep Sooch.
Dream Girl 2 is a 2023 Indian Hindi-language comedy-drama film directed by Raaj Shaandilyaa
and produced by Ekta Kapoor and Shobha Kapoor under Balaji Motion Pictures.
A spiritual sequel to the 2019 film Dream Girl, the film stars Ayushmann Khurrana, alongside an ensemble supporting cast, including
Ananya Panday, Paresh Rawal, Annu Kapoor, Rajpal Yadav, Vijay Raaz, Asrani, Abhishek Banerjee, Manjot Singh and Seema Pahwa.
The film is about a man who cross-dresses and disguises as
a woman, leading to chaos and confusion.
Principal photography began in August 2022 and ended in March 2023.
It was released theatrically on 25 August 2023.
The film received mixed reviews from critics.
It was a commercial success, grossing ₹140 crore worldwide, emerging
as the eleventh-highest grossing Hindi film of 2023.
It marked the final film appearance of Asrani
before his death on 20 October 2025.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.